	Danish 'da'	Default ''	Chinese 'zh'	English (Australia) 'en_AU'	Portuguese (Brazil) 'pt_BR'	Norwegian 'no'	Lithuanian 'lt'	Portuguese 'pt'	Dutch 'nl'	Korean 'ko'	German (Austria) 'de_AT'	German 'de'	Finnish 'fi'	Italian 'it'	French 'fr'	Spanish 'es'	Russian 'ru'	Swedish 'sv'	English (Brazil) 'en_BR'	English (Germany) 'en_DE'	Czech 'cs'	Slovak 'sk'	Hungarian 'hu'	Estonian 'et'	Latvian 'lv'	Sloven(ian) 'sl'
static.accountDetails		Account details							Rekeninggegevens			Kontoangaben									Upřesňující údaje o účtu	Detaily o účte	Számla adatai	Konto andmed	Detalizēta informācija par kontu	Podatki o računu
static.accountHolder		Account holder							Rekeninghouder			Kontoinhaber									Vlastník účtu	Majiteľ účtu	Számlatulajdonos	Konto omanik	Konta īpašnieks	Nosilec računa
static.accountNr		Account number							Rekeningnummer			Kontonummer								Kontonummer	Číslo účtu	Číslo účtu	Számlaszám	Konto number	Konta numurs	Številka računa
static.amount	Beløb	Amount	金额			Beløp	Suma	Valor	Bedrag	금액		Betrag	Summa	Importo	Somme	Cantidad	Сумма	Totalt Belopp			Částka	Suma	Mennyiség	Summa	Summa	Količina
static.backToMerchantLink	Færdig	Done				Ferdig	Atlikta	Concluído	Klaar			Abgeschlossen	Valmis	Completato	Terminé	Finalizado	Готово	Klar			Provedeno	Hotovo	Kész	Valmis	Gatavs	Končano
static.bankBranchNr		Clearing number							Clearingnummer 		Ausgleichsziffer 	BLZ								BLZ	Zúčtovací číslo	Klíringové číslo	Kifizetési szám	Kliiringunumber	Klīringa numurs	Obračunska številka
static.bankleitzahl		Bankleitzahl(BLZ)																								
static.bic		BIC																								
static.bpayInstructions		BPAY instructions copy text ....... Lorem ipsum dolor sit amet, consectetur adipiscing elit. Vestibulum interdum massa sit amet massa convallis ullamcorper. Nam sit amet lectus nisi. Cras elementum, lectus vel rutrum eleifend, mi est tempus odio, non ullamcorper ligula magna et enim. Lorem ipsum dolor sit amet, consectetur adipiscing elit. Vivamus eleifend congue elit, in ultrices justo sagittis feugiat. Sed posuere erat diam. Etiam sed erat nec tellus viverra ullamcorper ac at neque. Cras eget ipsum ut dui																								
static.bpayOriginatorLabel		Biller Code																			Účetní kód	Účtovný kód	Fizetési kód	Arvelduskood	Rēķina izrakstītāja kods	Koda izdajatelja računa
static.bpayReferenceLabel		Ref																			Variabilní symbol	Ref	Hiv.	Viitenumber	Ats.	Ref.
static.cancel	Annuller	Cancel	取消			Avbryt	Atšaukti	Cancelar	Annuleren	취소		Abbrechen	Peruuta	Annulla	Annuler	Cancelar	Отмена	Ångra			Storno	Zrušiť	Mégsem	Loobu	Atcelt	Prekliči
static.cardExpirationDate	Udløbsdato	Expiration date	终止日期			Utløpsdato	Galiojimo data	Data de validade	Vervaldatum	만료 날짜		Ablaufdatum	Luottokortin voimassaolo	Data di scadenza	Date d'expiration	Fecha de vencimiento	Дата окончания срока действия	Utgångs datum			Termín vypršení platnosti	Dátum skončenia platnosti	Lejárat dátuma	Aegumiskuupäev	Derīguma termiņš	Datum poteka
static.cardNumber	Kortnummer	Card number	卡号			Kortnummer	Kortelės numeris	Número de cartão	Vervaldatum	카드 번호		Kartennummer	Kortin numero	Numero della carta	Numéro de la carte	Número de tarjeta:	Номер карты	Kortnummer			Číslo karty	Číslo karty	Kártyaszám	Kaardi number	Kartes numurs	Številka kartice
static.cardStartDate	Startdato	Start date	起始日期			Startdato	Pradžios data	Data de início	Begindatum	시작 날짜		Startdatum	Aloituspäivämäärä	Data di inizio	Date de début	Fecha de comienzo	Дата начала	Start datum			Datum zahájení	Začiatok	Kezdési dátum	Alguskuupäev	Sākuma datums	Začetni datum
static.checkPaymentInstructionRefThreat		Please ensure you write your Payment reference on your check and do not enclose any letters with the check. If you do not write the Payment reference on the check we will not be able to process your payment.													Assurez-vous d'avoir inscrit votre référence de paiement sur votre chèque et ne joignez aucune lettre avec celui-ci. Si vous n'inscrivez pas votre référence de paiement sur votre chèque, nous ne pourrons pas traiter votre paiement.						Vyplňte, prosím, na šeku svůj variabilní symbol a nepřikládejte k šeku žádné dopisy. Pokud na šeku nevyplníte variabilní symbol, nebudeme schopni vaši platbu zpracovat.	Prosím, uistite sa, že na šeku uvediete referenčné číslo platby a neprikladajte k šeku žiadne listy. Ak referenčné číslo platby neuvediete na šek, platbu nebude možné spracovať.	Ügyeljen, hogy a csekkre írja rá a fizetési hivatkozási számát. A borítékba a csekken kívül ne tegyen mást. Ha nem írja rá a csekkre ezt a fizetési hivatkozási számot, kifizetését nem tudjuk feldolgozni.	Kirjutage tšekile kindlasti oma makseviide ja ärge saatke koos tšekiga kirju. Kui te makseviidet tšekile ei kirjuta, ei saa me teie makset töödelda.	Lūdzu, pārliecinieties, vai čekā ierakstījāt savu maksājuma atsauci, kā arī čekā neiekļaujiet nekādus burtus. Ja čekā neierakstīsit maksājuma atsauci, mēs nevarēsim apstrādāt jūsu maksājumu.	Prosimo, preverite, ali ste na ček napisali svojo referenco za plačilo in čeku ne prilagajte nobenih pisem. Če na ček ne napišete reference za plačilo, vašega plačila morda ne bomo mogli obdelati.
static.checkStartInstruction		Follow the instructions on the next page to pay by check.													Suivez les instructions de la page suivante pour payer par chèque.						Pro platbu šekem postupujte podle pokynů na další straně.	Pre platbu šekom sa pridržiavajte inštrukcií na nasledujúcej strane.	A csekkes fizetéshez kövesse a következő oldalán található utasításokat.	Tšekiga maksmiseks järgige järgmisel lehel esitatud juhiseid.	Izpildiet nākamajā lapā sniegtos norādījumus, lai maksātu ar čeku.	Za plačilo s čekom sledite navodilom na naslednji strani.
static.chk	Check	Check	支票			Cheque	čekis	Cheque	Cheque	수표		Scheck	Shekki	Assegno	Chèque	Cheque	Чек	Check			Šek	Šek	Csekk	Tšekk	Čeks	Ček
static.city	By	City	市			By	Miestas	Cidade	Stad	도시		Stadt	Kaupunki	Città	La ville	Ciudad	город	Stad			Město	Mesto	Város	Linn	Pilsētas	Mesto
static.cleRib		Clé RIB																								
static.clickOn		Click on																			Klikněte na	Kliknite na	Kattintás	Klõpsake	Noklikšķiniet uz	Kliknite
static.codeBank		Code banque																								
static.codeGuichet		Code guichet																								
static.codigoDeEntidad		Codigo de entidad																								
static.CodigoDeOficina		Codigo de oficina																								
static.creditCard	Kreditkort	Credit card	信用卡			Kredittkort	Kredito kortelė	Cartão de crédito	Creditcard	신용카드		Kreditkarte	Luottokortti	Carta di credito	Carte de crédit	Tarjeta de crédito	Кредитная карта	Kreditkort			Úvěrová karta	Kreditná karta	Bankkártya	Krediitkaart	Kredītkarte	Kreditna kartica
static.cvv	Sikkerhedskode (CVV)	Security code (CVV)	安全码(CVV)			Sikkerhetskode (CVV)	Saugos kodas (CVV)	Código de segurança (CVV)	Verificatiecode (CVV)	보안 코드(CVV)		Sicherheits-Code (CVV)	Turvakoodi (CVV)	Codice di sicurezza (CVV)	Code de sécurité (CVV)	Código de seguridad (CVV)	Код безопасности (CVV)	CVV-kod			Bezpečnostní kód (CVV)	Bezpečnostný kód (CVV)	Biztonsági kód (CVV)	Turbekood (CVV)	Drošības kods (CVV)	Varnostna koda (CVV)
static.cvvInfo	Kortverificeringskoden er en sikkerhedsfunktion til transaktioner med kredit- og hævekort, der giver øget beskyttelse mod kreditkortsvindel. På visakort og MasterCard er det de sidste tre kontrolcifre på bagsiden af kortet. De findes typisk i øverste højre hjørne af underskriftsfeltet.	Card Verification Code is a security feature for credit or debit card transactions, giving increased protection against credit card fraud. On Visa and MasterCard this is the last three digits on the back of your card, typically found in the right top of the signature strip.	信用卡验证码是针对信用卡或借记卡交易的安全性功能，它提高了对信用卡欺诈的防范。对于Visa和Master卡，该验证码是卡背面上的最后3位数字，通常出现在签名条的右上部。			Kortets sikkerhetskode er en sikkerhetsfunkjson for transaksjoner med kredit- eller debetkort, som gir økt beskyttelse mot kredittkortsvindel. På Visa og MasterCard er dette de tre siste sifrene på baksiden av kortet, vanligvis øverst til høyre på signaturlinjen.	Kortelės patvirtinimo kodas (CVV) yra kredito arba debeto kortelių operacijų saugos funkcija, suteikianti didesnę apsaugą nuo kredito kortelių sukčių. „Visa“ ir „MasterCard“ kortelėse tai yra trys paskutinieji skaičiai, nurodyti kortelės antroje pusėje, dažniausiai viršutiniame dešiniajame parašo juostelės kampe.	O Código de Verificação de Cartão é um recurso de segurança para as operações com cartão de débito e crédito, para aumentar a proteção contra fraudes com o cartão de crédito. No cartão Visa e MasterCard, são os 3 últimos dígitos localizados no verso do seu cartão, geralmente na parte superior direita acima do espaço de assinatura.	De kaartverificatiecode (Card Verification Code, CVV) is een beveiligingsfunctie bij creditcard- en debitcardtransacties en biedt extra bescherming tegen creditcardfraude. Bij Visa en MasterCard zijn dit de laatste drie cijfers achter op uw kaart, meestal rechtsboven in de handtekeningstrip.	CVV(Card Verification Code)는 신용카드 또는 직불카드 거래를 위한 보안 기능으로 신용카드 사기를 방지하기 위해 제공됩니다. Visa와 MasterCard의 CVV는 카드 뒷면에 있는 숫자의 마지막 3자리인데, 보통 서명란의 우측 상단에 있습니다.		"Der Karten-Verifizierungscode ist eine Sicherheitsfunktion für Transaktionen mit Kredit- oder Guthabenkarten; er bietet einen zusätzlichen Schutz gegen Kreditkartenbetrug. Bei Visa und MasterCard entspricht dieser Code den letzten drei Ziffern auf der Rückseite Ihrer Karte, normalerweise oben rechts im Unterschriftsstreifen."	Kortin vahvistuskoodi on turvaominaisuus credit- tai debit-korteilla tapahtuvia maksuja varten. Se auttaa suojaamaan luottokorttipetoksilta. Visa- ja MasterCard -korteissa koodi on kolme viimeistä numeroa korttisi takana, yleensä allekirjoituskohdan yläpuolella oikealla.	Il codice di verifica della carta (Card Verification Code) è una funzione di sicurezza per le transazioni eseguite con carta di credito o di debito per fornire una protezione maggiore contro le frodi. Nelle carte Visa e MasterCard è rappresentato dalle ultime tre cifre sul retro della carta, in genere in alto a destra della banda contenente la firma.	Le code de vérification est utilisée pour la vérification du titulaire de carte et aide à prévenir l'utilisation abusive des cartes. Pour Visa et Mastercard, la combinaison de trois chiffres est en outre le numéro de carte de crédit sur le dos de la carte imprimée dans la zone de signature.	El código de verificación de la tarjeta es una característica de seguridad para transacciones con tarjetas de crédito o débito que ofrece una mayor protección contra el uso fraudulento de las tarjetas. En las tarjetas Visa y MasterCard, este código es el número de tres cifras del reverso de la tarjeta, que se encuentra normalmente en la esquina superior derecha del espacio para la firma.	Верификационный номер карты – это способ обеспечения безопасности при совершении операций по кредитной или дебетовой карте, которая обеспечивает защиту от мошенничества с кредитными картами. На картах Visa и MasterCard это последние три цифры на обратной стороне карты, обычно они находятся в правой верхней части строки для подписи.	CVV-kod är en säkerhetskontroll för kreditkorts- och debit transaktioner, som ger ett ökat skydd mot kreditkortsbedrägerier. För Visa och MasterCard är det de tre sista siffrorna på baksidan av ditt kort och brukar finns högst upp till höger på signaturremsan.			Ověřovací kód karty je bezpečnostní prvek transakcí s úvěrovou nebo platební kartou, který zvyšuje zabezpečení karty proti zneužití. Na kartách Visa a MasterCard to jsou poslední tři číslice na rubu karty, typicky se nacházejí v pravém horním rohu podpisového pruhu.	Bezpečnostný kód (Card Verification Code) je bezpečnostný prvok pre kreditné alebo debetné kartové transakcie, ktorý zvyšuje ochranu voči zneužitiu. Na kartách Visa a MasterCard ide o posledné trojčíslie na zadnej strane karty, zvyčajne v pravom hornom rohu pásu určeného na podpis.	A kártyaellenőrzési kód a bank- és hitelkártyák egy biztonsági funkciója, mely fokozott védelmet biztosít az illetéktelen felhasználással szemben. A Visa és a MasterCard esetén ez egy 3 jegyű szám a kártya hátoldalán, általában az aláírási sáv jobb szélénél.	Kaardi valideerimiskood on krediit- ja deebetkaarditehingute turbefunktsioon, mis kaitseb tõhusalt krediitkaardipettuste eest. Krediitkaartidel Visa ja MasterCard on koodiks kolm viimast numbrit kaardi tagaküljel (tavaliselt allkirjariba parempoolses ülanurgas).	Kartes pārbaudes kods (Card Verification Code — CVV) ir kredītkaršu un debetkaršu transakciju drošības līdzeklis, kas uzlabo aizsardzību pret kredītkaršu krāpniecību. Visa un MasterCard kartēm tie ir trīs pēdējie cipari kartes aizmugurē, parasti paraksta joslas augšdaļā pa labi.	"Koda za verifikacijo kartice (ang. ""Card Verification Code - CVV"") je element varnosti za transakcije s kreditnimi ali debetnimi karticami, ki nudi višjo stopnjo zaščite pred goljufijami s kreditnimi karticami. Pri karticah Visa in MasterCard predstavljajo to kodo zadnje tri številke na hrbtni strani vaše kartice. Običajno se številke nahajajo na zgornjem desnem robu traku s podpisom."
static.cvvInfoWindow	Kortsikkerhedskoden er en 3- eller 4-cifret kode, der er præget eller tryk på den modsatte side af Visa, MasterCard og Discover-kort og på forsiden af American Express-kort. Bemærk: Kortsikkerhedskoden er ikke de sidste 3 eller 4 tal i kreditkortnummeret. Det er en ekstra sikkerhedsforanstaltning for at sikre, at du har adgang til er i fysisk besiddelse af selve kreditkortet for at du kan angive kortsikkerhedskoden. Se nedenfor for nærmere oplysninger om, hvor du kan finde kortsikkerhedskoden.	The Card Security Code is a 3 or 4 digit code embossed or imprinted on the reverse side of Visa, MasterCard and Discover cards and on the front of American Express cards. Please note: The card security code is not the last 3 or 4 digits of your credit card number. This is an extra security measure to ensure that you have access or physical possession of  the credit card itself in order to use the Card Security Code. For details on where to find your Card Security Code, please check below.	信用卡安全代码是凹刻或突出在Visa、MasterCard和Discover卡背面和American Express卡正面的3位或4位数字。请注意： 信用卡安全代码并不是信用卡卡号的后3位或4位数字。这种额外的安全措施是为了通过您提供的信用卡安全代码来确认您完全可以使用或实际拥有信用卡实物。如需了解信用卡安全代码的详细情况，请查看下列内容。			Kortets sikkerhetskode er en tre- eller firesifret kode som er preget eller trykt på baksiden av kort fra Visa, MasterCard og Discover og på forsiden av kort fra American Express . Merk: Kortets sikkerhetskode er ikke de siste tre eller fire sifrene i kredittkortnummeret. Dette er en ekstra sikkerhet som bekrefter at du har tilgang til kortet eller er i fysisk besittelse av selve kredittkortet, slik at du kan bruke kortets sikkerhetskode. Nedenfor finner du opplysninger om hvor du finner kortets sikkerhetskode.	Kortelės saugos kodas – tai 3 arba 4 skaitmenų kodas, įspaustas arba išspausdintas antroje „Visa“, „MasterCard“ ir „Discover“ kortelių pusėje ir „American Express“ kortelių priekyje. Atminkite: kortelės saugos kodas nėra 3 ar 4 jūsų kredito kortelės numerio skaitmenys. Tai papildoma apsauga, užtikrinanti prieigą prie kredito kortelės arba fizinį jos naudojimą norint naudoti kortelės saugos kodą. Jei norite sužinoti, kur rasti kortelės saugos kodą, žr. toliau.	O Código de Segurança do Cartão é um código de 3 ou 4 dígitos gravado ou impresso no verso dos cartões Visa, MasterCard e Discover e na frente dos cartões American Express. Observação: O código de segurança do cartão não são os 3 ou 4 últimos dígitos do número do seu cartão de crédito. Esta é uma medida extra de segurança para garantir que você tem acesso ou está com o cartão em mãos no momento do pedido para usar o Código de Segurança do Cartão. Para detalhes sobre como localizar o Código de Segurança do Cartão, veja abaixo.	De kaartverificatiecode is een code van drie of vier cijfers die gedrukt of in reliëf op de achterzijde van een Visa-, MasterCard- en Discover-creditcard te vinden is en op de voorzijde van een American Express-creditcard. Let wel: De verificatiecode is niet hetzelfde als de laatste drie of vier cijfers van uw creditcardnummer. Het is een extra beveiligingsmaatregel om er zeker van te zijn dat u toegang hebt tot of fysiek in het bezit bent van de creditcard en zodoende de verificatiecode kunt gebruiken. Voor meer gegevens over waar u de verificatiecode kunt vinden, raadpleegt u het onderstaande.	카드 보안 코드는 3자리 또는 4자리 숫자 코드로 Visa, MasterCard, Discover 카드는 뒷면에, American Express 카드는 앞면에 있습니다. 참고: 카드 보안 코드는 신용카드 번호의 마지막 3자리 또는 4자리 숫자가 아닙니다. 카드 보안 코드는 신용카드의 소유권과 접근권을 확인하기 위한 특별 보안 조치입니다. 카드 보안 코드가 어디에 있는지 확인하려면 아래를 확인하십시오.		Der Kreditkarten-Sicherheitscode ist ein 3-4 stelliger Code, der auf der Rückseite Ihrer Visa, MasterCard und Discover Card und auf der Vorderseite Ihrer American Express Card abgedruckt ist. Bitte beachten: Beim Kreditkarten-Sicherheitscode handelt es sich nicht um die letzten 3 oder 4 Stellen Ihrer Kreditkartennummer. Dies ist eine zusätzliche Sicherheitsmaßnahme, um Missbrauch zu vermeiden. Durch die Angabe dieses Codes wird sichergestellt, dass sich die Karte auch tatsächlich in Ihrem Besitz befindet. Weitere Informationen, wo der Sicherheitscode auf Ihrer Kreditkarte abgedruckt ist, finden Sie weiter unten.	Kortin tarkistusnumero on 3- tai 4-numeroinen koodi, joka on kohokuvioitu tai kaiverrettu Visa-, MasterCard- ja Discover-korttien kääntöpuolelle ja American Express -kortin etupuolelle. Huomaathan: Kortin turvakoodi ei ole 3 tai 4 viimeistä luottokorttisi numeroa. Tämä on lisäturvallisuustoimenpide, jolla varmistetaan että sinulla on saatavilla tai fyysisesti hallussasi luottokortti sen tarkistusnumeron käyttämiseksi. Katso alta lisätietoja mistä kortin tarkistusnumero löytyy.	Il codice di sicurezza della carta è un codice di tre o quattro cifre riportato sul retro delle carte Visa, MasterCard e Discover e sulla parte anteriore delle carte American Express. Si prega di notare che: Il codice di sicurezza della carta non corrisponde alle ultime 3 o 4 cifre del numero della carta. Si tratta di una misura di sicurezza addizionale, studiata per far sì che l'utente sia fisicamente in possesso della carta di credito per eseguire le transazioni. Per ulteriori informazioni sulla posizione del codice di sicurezza, vedere sotto.	Le code de vérification est marquée de trois ou combinaison à quatre chiffres du numéro ou imprimé sur le dos des cartes Visa, MasterCard et Discover et sur le front de l'American Express. S'il vous plaît noter que les numéros ne correspondent pas à la vérification des 3 ou 4 derniers chiffres de votre numéro de carte. La requête de la vérification est une mesure de sécurité pour confirmer que vous êtes en possession physique de la carte. Pour plus d'informations sur l'endroit où est la vérification de la carte sur votre carte, coordonnées ci-dessous.	El código de seguridad de la tarjeta es un código de 3 o 4 dígitos en relieve o impreso en el reverso de las tarjetas Visa, MasterCard y Discover y en el anverso de las tarjetas American Express. Tenga presente que: El código de seguridad de la tarjeta no corresponde a los 3 o 4 últimos dígitos del número de la tarjeta de crédito. Se trata de una medida adicional de seguridad para garantizar que tiene acceso a la tarjeta de crédito o que la posee físicamente para poder utilizar el código de seguridad de la tarjeta. Para obtener más información sobre dónde encontrar el código de seguridad de la tarjeta, consulte la información que se proporciona a continuación.	Код безопасности карты состоит из 3 или 4 цифр, выполненных тиснением или оттиском на оборотной стороне карт Visa, MasterCard и Discover, а также на лицевой стороне карт American Express. Обратите внимание: Код безопасности карты – это не последние 3 или 4 цифры номера карты. Это дополнительная мера безопасности, чтобы убедиться, что Вы имеете доступ или физически владеете кредитной картой для использования кода безопасности карты. Подробнее о том, где найти Ваш код безопасности карты, см. ниже.	Kortets CVV-kod är en 3 eller 4 siffrig kod präglad eller tryckt på baksidan av Visa-, MasterCard- eller Discoverkort och på framsidan av American Expresskort. OBS: CVV-koden är inte de sista 3 eller 4 siffrorna av ditt kreditkortsnummer. Detta är en extra kontroll för att säkerställa att du har fysisk tillgång till kreditkortet när du använder det. Se nedan för detaljer om vart du kan hitta kortets CVV-kod.			Bezpečnostní kód karty je 3ciferné nebo 4ciferné číslo vylisované nebo vytištěné na druhé straně karet Visa, MasterCard a Discover a na přední straně karet American Express. Upozornění: Bezpečnostní kód karty nejsou poslední 3 nebo 4 číslice čísla úvěrové karty. Toto je dodatečné bezpečnostní opatření pro zajištění toho, že máte k úvěrové kartě přístup nebo jste jejím vlastníkem, abyste mohl použít bezpečnostní kód karty. Pro podrobnosti o tom, kde najdete bezpečnostní kód své karty, zaškrtněte níže.	Bezpečnostný kód karty sú tri alebo štyri číslice vyrazené alebo vytlačené na zadnej strane kárt Visa, MasterCard a Discover a na prednej strane v prípade kariet American Express. Poznámka: Bezpečnostný kód netvoria posledné tri alebo štyri číslice čísla kreditnej karty. Ide o dodatočný bezpečnostný prvok, ktorý má overiť, či máte prístup alebo fyzicky vlastníte kreditnú kartu a poznáte tak bezpečnostný kód karty. Viac informácií o tom, kde sa nachádza bezpečnostný kód karty, nájdete nižšie.	A biztonsági kód egy 3 vagy 4 jegyű kód, amely a Visa, MasterCard és Discover kártyák hátoldalán, illetve az American Express kártyák elülső oldalán dombornyomással vagy nyomtatva látható. Kérjük, vegye figyelembe a következőket: A kártya biztonsági kódja nem a bankkártyaszám utolsó 3 vagy 4 számjegye. A kártya biztonsági kódja egy olyan kiegészítő biztonsági lépés, amellyel azt ellenőrizzük, hogy valóban Önhöz tartozik-e kártya, illetve van-e hozzáférése hozzá. A kártya biztonsági kódjának helyéről további részleteket a továbbiakban talál.	Kaardi turbekood on kolme- või neljanumbriline reljeefne või sissepressitud kood kaartide Visa, MasterCard ja Discover tagaküljel ja American Expressi kaardi esiküljel. Märkus. Teie krediitkaardi kolm või neli viimast numbrit ei ole kaardi turbekood. See on täiendav turbemeede, mis eeldab, et teil on kaardi turbekoodi kasutamiseks juurdepääs krediitkaardile või krediitkaart on füüsiliselt teie käes. Üksikasjaliku teabe kaardi turbekoodi asukoha kohta leiate altpoolt.	Kartes drošības kods ir 3 vai 4 ciparu kods, kas iegravēts vai iespiests Visa, MasterCard un Discover karšu aizmugurē un American Express karšu priekšpusē. Lūdzu, ņemiet vērā: Šis kartes drošības kods nav jūsu kredītkartes numura pēdējie 3 vai 4 cipari. Šis ir papildu drošības līdzeklis, lai pārliecinātos, vai jums ir piekļuve pašai kredītkartei vai esat tās īpašnieks un varat izmantot kartes drošības kodu. Detalizētu informāciju par to, kā varat atrast savas kartes drošības kodu, lūdzu, skatiet tālāk.	Varnostna koda kartice je 3- ali 4-številčna koda, reliefno odtisnjena ali vtisnjena na hrbtni strani kartic Visa, MasterCard in Discover oz. na sprednji strani kartic American Express. Prosimo, bodite pozorni: Varnostne kode kartice ne predstavljajo zadnje 3 ali 4 številke vaše kreditne kartice. To je dodaten varnostni ukrep, ki zagotavlja, da imate dostop ali fizični nadzor nad samo kreditno kartico, kadar uporabite varnostno kodo kartice. Podrobnosti o tem, kje na kartici najdete varnostno kodo kartice, so navedene v nadaljevanju.
static.dd		SEPA Direct Debit							Automatische afschrijving			Elektronischen Lastschriftverfahren (ELV)									Přímé inkaso	Bezhotovostná platba	Közvetlen levonás	Otsekorraldus	Tiešais debets	Neposredna obremenitev
static.ddAccountStatementInfo		Your payment will be handled by Digital River World Payments AB. This name may appear on your account statement.							Uw betaling wordt verwerkt door Digital River World Payments AB. Deze naam wordt eventueel op uw rekeningoverzicht weergegeven.			Ihre Zahlung wird von Digital River World Payments AB bearbeitet. Dieser Name erscheint eventuell auf Ihrem Kontoauszug.									Vaši platbu zprostředkuje Digital River World Payments AB. Toto jméno se může objevit na vašem výpisu z účtu.	O priebeh platby sa postará Digital River World Payments AB. Tento názov sa môže objaviť na výpise z účtu.	A fizetést a Digital River World Payments AB kezeli. A számlakivonaton ez a név fog szerepelni.	Teie makset käitleb Digital River World Payments AB. See nimi võidakse kuvada teie konto väljavõttel.	Jūsu maksājumu apstrādās Digital River World Payments AB. Šis nosaukums, iespējams, būs norādīts jūsu konta pārskatā.	Vaše plačilo bo opravilo podjetje Digital River World Payments AB. To ime se lahko pojavi na vašem izpisku računa.
static.ddConsentText		I hereby declare that the account details provided belong to me. I further approve that Digital River World Payments AB debits the same account as a payment for my order placed at [Merchant Name]							Ik verklaar hierbij dat de opgegeven rekeninginformatie aan mij toebehoort. Daarnaast ga ik ermee akkoord dat Digital River World Payments AB deze zelfde rekening debiteert als betaling voor mijn bestelling bij [Merchant name].			Hiermit ermächtige(n) ich / wir Sie widerruflich, die von mir / uns zu entrichtenden Zahlungen bei Fälligkeit zu Lasten meines / unseres oben angegebenen Kontos durch Lastschrift einzuziehen. Wenn mein / unser Konto die erforderliche Deckung nicht aufweist, besteht seitens des kontoführenden Kreditinstitutes keine Verpflichtung zur Einlösung.									Tímto prohlašuji, že poskytnuté upřesňující údaje o účtu náležejí mně. Dále souhlasím s tím, aby Digital River World Payments AB zaúčtovala na stejný účet platbu za mou objednávku učiněnou u [Merchant Name]	Týmto prehlasujem, že poskytnuté údaje o účte patria mne. Ďalej potvrdzujem, že Digital River World Payments AB stiahla z účtu sumu vo výške platby za objednávku u [Merchant Name]	Kijelentem, hogy a saját számlámmal kapcsolatos adatokat adtam meg. Ezennel felhatalmazom a Digital River World Payments AB céget, hogy ugyanezen számlát a(z) [Merchant Name] cégnél történt rendelés ellenértékével megterhelje.	Käesolevaga kinnitan, et esitatud kontoandmed kuuluvad minule. Lisaks nõustun sellega, et Digital River World Payments AB debiteerib seda kontot, et tasuda minu tellimuse eest, mille esitasin kauplusele [Merchant Name]	Ar šo es apliecinu, ka norādīta mana konta detalizētā informācija. Papildus apstiprinu, ka Digital River World Payments AB debetē to pašu kontu kā maksājumu par manu pasūtījumu, kas veikts pie pārdevēja [Merchant Name].	Izjavljam, da so navedeni podatki o računu moji. Poleg tega dajem dovoljenje, da podjetje Digital River World Payments AB obremeni isti račun za plačilo mojega naročila, ki sem ga oddal/a [Merchant Name].
static.dddsRedirectInfo	Dit kort er omfattet af 3D Secure. Du bliver stillet videre til din bank, hvor du skal have godkendelse.	Your card is 3D Secure enrolled. You will be redirected to your bank for authentication.	您的信用卡已经过3D Secure注册。您将被重定向到您的银行以进行验证。			Ditt kort er registrert for 3-D Secure. Du vil bli ført videre til din bankforbindelse for autentisering.	Jūsų kortelėje naudojama 3D apsauga. Būsite nukreipti į banką autentiškumui patvirtinti.	Seu cartão possui segurança 3D. Você será redirecionado para seu banco para autenticação.	Uw kaart is geregistreerd bij 3-D Secure. U wordt voor verificatie omgeleid naar uw bank.	귀하의 카드는 3D Secure에 등록되어 있습니다. 인증을 위해 귀하의 은행으로 이동합니다.		Ihre Karte ist für 3D Secure eingetragen. Sie werden zur Authentifizierung an Ihre Bank umgeleitet.	Korttisi on mukana 3D Securessa. Sinut ohjataan pankkiisi tunnistusta varten.	La tua carta è registrata 3D Secure. Verrai indirizzato alla tua banca per l'identificazione.	Votre carte est activée pour le processus de 3D Secure. Vous sera transmis à votre banque si vous pouvez vérifier avec votre code personnel.	Su tarjeta está protegida con el sistema 3D Secure. Será redireccionado a su banco para su autenticación.	Ваша карта защищена с помощью технологии 3D Secure. Для идентификации Вы будете перенаправлены в свой банк.	Ditt kort är aktiverat för 3DS. Du kommer skickas vidare till din bank för autentisiering.			Vaše karta je zaregistrována podle standardu zabezpečení 3-D Secure. Budete přesměrován do své banky pro ověření.	Vaša karta je chránená protokolom 3D Secure. Budete presmerovaný do vašej banky na overenie.	Az Ön kártyája 3D Secure besorolású. A hitelesítéshez az oldal átirányítódik a bank oldalára.	Teie kaart kuulub turbesüsteemi 3D Secure. Teid suunatakse autentimiseks edasi teie panka.	Jūsu kartei tiek izmantots protokols 3D Secure. Jūs tiksit novirzīts uz savu banku autentificēšanai.	Vaša kartica je registrirana za storitev 3D Secure. Za overovitev boste preusmerjeni na svojo banko.
static.digits		digits																								
static.eft	Bankoverførsel	Wire Transfer		Bpay	Boleto Bancário	Bankoverføring	Pervedimas	Transferência Eletrônica	Bankoverschrijving	Fund Transfer		Überweisung	Tilisiirto	Bonifico	Virement bancaire	Transferencia bancaria	Электронный перевод	Plusgiro	Boleto Bancário		Telegrafický převod	Elektronický prevod	Távirati utalás	Elektrooniline ülekanne	Elektroniskais pārskaitījums	Elektronski prenos
static.eftCollectionAgency	[Merchant Name] anvender Digital River World Payments AB til håndtering af din betaling.	[Merchant Name] is using Digital River World Payments AB as a collection agency for your payment.				[Merchant Name] bruker Digital River World Payments AB som betalingsagent for din betaling.	[Merchant Name] naudoja Digital River World Payments AB kaip jūsų įmokų surinkimo agentūrą.		[Merchant Name] maakt gebruik van de service van Digital River World Payments AB als incassobureau voor uw betaling.			[Merchant Name] verwendet Digital River World Payments AB als Inkassostelle für Ihre Zahlung.	[Merchant Name] käyttää Digital River World Payments AB:tä maksun välittäjänä.	[Merchant Name] si avvale dei servizi di Digital River World Payments AB per ricevere i pagamenti.	[Merchant Name] utilise Digital River World Payments AB comme agence de collecte pour votre paiement.	[Merchant Name] utiliza Digital River World Payments AB como agencia de cobro para realizar su pago.	[Merchant Name] для вашего платежа использует Digital River World Payments AB в качестве агентства по сбору платежей.	[Merchant Name] använder Digital River World Payments AB som betalningsagent för din betalning.			[Merchant Name] využívá Digital River World Payments AB jako inkasní agentury vaší platby.	[Merchant Name] využíva Digital River World Payments AB ako inkasnú agentúru platieb.	A(z) [Merchant Name] kifizetéséhez a Digital River World Payments AB mint beszedő ügynökség segítségét veszi igénybe.	[Merchant Name] kasutab ettevõtet Digital River World Payments AB maksete sissenõudmise asutusena.	[Merchant Name] izmanto Digital River World Payments AB kā iekasēšanas aģentūru jūsu maksājuma saņemšanai.	[Merchant Name] uporablja podjetje Digital River World Payments AB kot zbirno agencijo za vaše plačilo.
static.eftPaymentBodyInfo	Følg betalingsoplysningerne, når du skal overføre penge til vores bankkonto.	Follow the payment instructions to transfer money to our bank account.				Følg betalingsanvisningene for å overføre penger til vår bankkonto.	Vykdykite kitame puslapyje pateiktus nurodymus, kad pervestumėte pinigus į savo banko sąskaitą.	Siga as instruções de pagamento para transferir dinheiro para nossa conta corrente.	Volg de betalingsaanwijzingen op de volgende pagina om geld over te maken naar onze bankrekening.			Folgen Sie den Zahlungshinweisen, um Geld auf unser Bankkonto zu überweisen.	Noudata maksuohjeita siirtääksesi rahaa pankkitilillemme.	Segui le istruzioni di pagamento per trasferire denaro sul nostro conto bancario	Suivez les modalités de paiement pour transférer la somme sur notre compte bancaire.	Siga las instrucciones de pago para transferir el dinero a nuestra cuenta bancaria.	Для перечисления денег на наш банковский счет следуйте инструкциям, приведенным на следующей странице.	Följ betalningsanvisningarna för att föra över pengar till vårt plusgirokonto.			Sledujte platební pokyny pro převod peněz na váš bankovní účet.	Na prevod peňazí na náš účet sa pridržiavajte inštrukcií pre platby.	A bankszámlánkra történő utaláshoz kövesse a kifizetési utasításokat.	Raha ülekandmiseks meie pangakontole järgige maksejuhiseid.	Izpildiet norādījumus par maksājumu, lai pārskaitītu naudu uz mūsu bankas kontu.	Za prenos denarja na naš bančni račun sledite navodilom za plačilo.
static.eftPaymentHeadInfo	Din bestilling er modtaget og afventer betaling. Foretag din betaling nu for at afslutte din ordre.	Your order has been received and is awaiting payment. Please make your payment now to complete your order.				Bestillingen din er mottatt og venter på betaling. Foreta betalingen nå for å fullføre bestillingen.	Jūsų užsakymas gautas ir laukiama mokėjimo. Norėdami užbaigti užsakymą, dabar atlikite mokėjimą.	Seu pedido foi recebido e está aguardando o pagamento. Por favor, faça o pagamento neste momento para finalizar o pedido.	Uw bestelling is ontvangen en wacht op betaling. Maak uw betaling nu over om uw bestelling te voltooien.			Ihre Bestellung ist eingegangen und zur Zahlung fällig. Bitte nehmen Sie nun die Zahlung vor, um Ihre Bestellung abzuschließen.  	Tilauksesi on otettu vastaan ja odottaa maksua. Suorita maksu nyt päättääksesi tilauksesi.	L'ordine è stato ricevuto ed è in attesa di pagamento. Effettua il pagamento ora per completare l'ordine.	Votre commande a été enregistrée et nous attendons votre paiement. Merci d'effectuer votre paiement maintenant pour terminer votre commande.	Su pedido ha sido recibido y está a la espera de que se reciba el pago. Realice el pago ahora para completar su pedido.	Ваш заказ был принят и находится в состоянии ожидания оплаты. Произведите оплату для его завершения.	Din order har blivit emottagen och väntar på betalning. Utför betalningen nu för att slutföra din order.			Vaše objednávka byla přijata a čeká na vyřízení platby. Prosím, proveďte nyní svoji platbu a dokončete objednávku.	Vaša objednávka bola spracovaná a čaká na prijatie platby. Vykonajte platbu teraz a dokončite objednávku.	Rendelését rögzítettük, kifizetésre vár. Kérjük, hogy a rendelés befejezéséhez a fizetést indítsa el most.	Teie tellimus on vastu võetud ja ootab maksmist. Tellimuse lõpuleviimiseks tehke makse kohe.	Jūsu pasūtījums ir saņemts, un tiek gaidīts maksājums. Lūdzu, nekavējoties veiciet maksājumu, lai pabeigtu savu pasūtījumu.	Vaše naročilo je bilo sprejeto in čakamo na plačilo. Prosimo, opravite plačilo, da dokončate izvedbo naročila.
static.eftPaymentInstructionDateThreatEnd	Din ordre sendes, når vi har modtaget bekræftelse på, at vores bank har modtaget beløbet. Det vil tage cirka [Days to deliver] dage.	Your order will be sent after we receive confirmation that our bank has received your funds. This will take approximately [Days to deliver] days.				Etter at vi får bekreftet fra banken vår at betalingen er mottatt, blir ordren sendt. Dette vil ta ca. [Days to deliver] dager.	Užsakymas bus išsiųstas, kai gausime patvirtinimą, kad jūsų bankas gavo lėšas. Tai užtruks maždaug penkias dienas.	Seu pedido será despachado depois que recebermos a confirmação de que o nosso banco recebeu o valor. Esse processo leva aproximadamente [Days to deliver] dias.	hebben ontvangen, wordt de bestelling geannuleerd. Zodra wij van onze bank bevestiging hebben gekregen dat uw betaling is ontvangen, wordt uw bestelling verzonden. Dit neemt ongeveer [days to deliver] dagen in beslag.			nicht eingegangen ist. Ihre Bestellung wird verschickt, nachdem der Zahlungseingang von unserer Bank bestätigt wurde. Dies dauert normalerweise ca. [days to deliver] Tage.	Kun olemme saaneet vahvistuksen, että pankkimme on saanut maksusi, lähetämme tilausvahvistuksesi. Se kestää noin [Days to deliver] päivää.	L'ordine sarà spedito dopo il ricevimento della conferma da parte della nostra banca dell'avvenuto accredito del pagamento. Quest'operazione richiede circa [Days to deliver] giorni.	Nous vous ferons parvenir votre commande dès que notre banque nous aura confirmé avoir reçu votre paiement. Cela prendra approximativement [Days to deliver] jours.	Se le enviará la confirmación del pedido una vez que recibamos confirmación de que su banco ha recibido sus fondos. Esto se realizará aproximadamente en [Days to deliver] días.	, ваш заказ будет аннулирован. Ваш заказ будет отправлен, как только мы получим подтверждение о поступлении средств на наш банковский счет. Это займет около пяти дней.	Din order skickas efter att vi har fått en bekträftelse från vår bank att betalningen är emottagen. Detta tar ca [Days to deliver] dagar.			Vámi objednané zboží bude odesláno, jakmile od své banky obdržíme potvrzení, že přijala Vaši platbu. Bude to trvat přibližně [Days to deliver] dnů.	Po doručení potvrdenia o prijatí platby našou bankou vám odošleme potvrdenie objednávky. To bude trvať približne [Days to deliver] dní.	Amint megerősítést kapunk arról, hogy az összeg beérkezett bankunkhoz, megküldjük a rendelés visszaigazolását. Ez a folyamat körülbelül [Days to deliver] napot vesz igénybe.	Teie tellimus täidetakse pärast seda, kui oleme saanud kinnituse, et teie makse on laekunud meie panka. Selleks kulub ligikaudu [Days to deliver] päeva.	Jūsu pasūtītās preces tiks nosūtītas, tiklīdz saņemsim apstiprinājumu, ka mūsu banka ir saņēmusi jūsu naudas līdzekļus. Tam būs nepieciešamas aptuveni [Days to deliver] dienas.	Vaše naročilo bomo posredovali naprej takoj, ko bomo prejeli potrditev, da je naša banka prejela vaš denar. Ta postopek traja približno [Days to deliver] dni.
static.eftPaymentInstructionDateThreatStart	Din bestilling annulleres, hvis betaling ikke modtages inden	Your order will be cancelled if your payment is not received before				Hvis betaling ikke er mottatt innen , blir ordren annullert.	Užsakymas bus atšauktas, jei mokėjimo negausime iki	Seu pedido será cancelado se o pagamento não for efetuado antes de	Als wij de betaling niet vóór			Ihre Bestellung wird storniert, wenn die Zahlung bis	Tilauksesi peruutetaan, jos maksusi ei ole saapunut perille ennen	In caso di mancata ricezione del pagamento, l'ordine sarà cancellato.	Votre commande sera annulée si votre paiement ne nous parvient pas avant	Su pedido se cancelará si no recibimos el pago antes del	Если платеж не будет получен до	Din order blir annulerad om betalningen inte är emottagen innan			Když před tím neobdržíme vaši platbu, vaše objednávka bude zrušena	Objednávka sa zruší, ak vašu platbu neprijmeme do	Rendelését töröljük, ha a fizetés nem történik meg a következő határidőig:	Teie tellimus tühistatakse, kui makse pole laekunud enne	Jūsu pasūtījums tiks atcelts, ja maksājums netiks saņemts pirms	Če vašega plačila ne prejmemo prej, kot v tem roku, bo vaše naročilo preklicano.
static.eftPaymentInstructionDetail	Giv dit pengeinstitut følgende anvisninger for at gennemføre din betaling	Provide your bank with the following instruction to complete your payment				Gi banken din følgende instruksjon for å gjennomføre betalingen	Pateikite bankui šiuos mokėjimo nurodymus	Forneça a seguinte instrução para seu banco para finalizar o pagamento	Geef uw bank de volgende aanwijzingen om uw betaling te voltooien			Geben Sie folgende Informationen für Ihre Bank ein, um die Zahlung abzuschließen	Anna pankillesi seuraavat ohjeet maksun suorittamista varten	Fornisci alla tua banca le seguenti istruzioni per completare il pagamento	Veuillez fournir à votre banque les instructions suivantes pour réaliser votre paiement	proporcione a su banco las siguientes instrucciones para realizar el pago	Предоставьте вашему банку следующие сведения для электронного перевода	Ge din bank följande information för att slutföra din betalning			Pro dokončení své platby vydejte své bance následující pokyny	Zadajte svojej banke nasledujúci príkaz na dokončenie platby	A fizetés során az alábbi adatokat kell bankja részére megadnia	Makse lõpuleviimiseks andke oma pangale edasi järgmised juhised	Sniedziet savai bankai šos norādījumus, lai pabeigtu savu maksājumu	Svoji banki predložite naslednja navodila za dokončanje vašega plačila
static.eftPaymentInstructionPrintHint	Udskriv denne side til brug for dit regnskab, da alle bankdetaljer kræves for at foretage din betaling. Bestillinger, som måtte blive afgivet uden alle ovenstående oplysninger, kan ikke ekspederes. Bemærk, at du kun bør betale for en ordre per betaling.	Print this page for your records as all bank details are required to make your payment. Orders placed without all of the above information may not be processed. Please note that you should only pay for one order per payment.				"Skriv ut denne siden som referanse; alle bankopplysninger er nødvendige for å foreta betalingen. Bestillinger som legges inn uten all ovenstående informasjon, kan risikere ikke å bli behandlet. Hver betaling skal kun gjelde én enkelt ordre."	Išspausdinkite šį puslapį, nes atliekant mokėjimą reikalinga visa banko informacija. Užsakymai be visos anksčiau nurodytos informacijos gali būti neapdorojami.	Imprima e guarde esta página, pois todos os detalhes do banco são necessários para efetuar o pagamento. É importante observar que você deve pagar somente um pedido por transação de pagamento.	Druk deze pagina voor uw administratie af aangezien alle bankdetails vereist zijn om uw betaling te voldoen. Bestellingen die zonder alle bovengenoemde gegevens worden geplaatst, kunnen niet worden verwerkt. Let wel dat u per betaling maar één bestelling kan betalen.			Drucken Sie bitte diese Seite für Ihre Unterlagen aus, da Sie alle Bankangaben benötigen, um die Zahlung durchführen zu können. Aufträge, die nicht alle erforderlichen Angaben aufweisen, werden unter Umständen nicht bearbeitet. Bitte beachten Sie, dass Sie Zahlungen immer nur für eine Bestellung leisten sollten.	Tulosta tämä sivu ja säilytä se, koska kaikki pankkiyksityiskohdat tarvitaan maksun suorittamiseen. Tilauksia ei voida mahdollisesti käsitellä ilman kaikkia yllä olevia tietoja. Ota huomioon, että sinun tulee suorittaa maksu vain yhdestä tilauksesta kerrallaan.	Stampa questa pagina per tuo riferimento, in quanto per il pagamento sono richieste tutte le coordinate bancarie. Gli ordini non completi di questi dati non potranno essere elaborati. Ti raccomandiamo di effettuare un solo pagamento per ciascun ordine.	Imprimez cette page pour vos dossiers car tous les détails bancaires sont requis pour faire votre paiement. Les commandes effectuées sans la totalité des renseignements ci-dessus ne pourront être traitées. Veuillez noter que vous ne devez payer qu'une commande par paiement.	Imprima esta página y consérvela, puesto que necesitará todos los datos bancarios para efectuar el pago. Los pedidos realizados sin toda la información anterior puede que no se procesen. Tenga en cuenta que solo deberá pagar una orden por cada referencia.	Распечатайте эту страницу для собственных заметок, поскольку банковские реквизиты необходимы для осуществления платежа. Заказы, размещенные без указания всех данных, указанных выше, могут быть не обработаны.	Skriv ut denna sida som referens, all bankinformation behövs för att slutföra din betalning. Ordrar lagda utan ovan information riskerar att inte bli behandlade. Varje betalning ska bara gälla en order.			Vytiskněte a uschovejte tuto stránku, protože pro platbu jsou zapotřebí všechny údaje banky. Objednávky, které nemají všechny výše uvedené náležitosti, nesmějí být zpracovány. Uvědomte si, prosím, že každou platbou smíte platit jen za jednu objednávku.	Vytlačte si túto stranu, údaje o bankovom spojení budete potrebovať pri zadávaní platby. Objednávky vytvorené bez všetkých vyššie uvedených informácií nemusia byť spracované. Prosím, všimnite si, že jednou platbou môžete zaplatiť len za jednu objednávku.	Nyomtassa ki ezt az oldalt emlékeztetőnek, mivel a kifizetéshez minden banki adat szükséges. Amennyiben rendelése során nem ad meg minden fenti adatot, előfordulhat, hogy rendelése nem kerül feldolgozásra. Vegye figyelembe, hogy egy kifizetéssel csak egy rendelést fizethet ki.	Printige see leht välja ja hoidke alles, sest makse tegemiseks peavad kõik nõutavad pangaandmed olema sisestatud. Tellimused, mis ei sisalda kogu ülalnimetatud teavet, võivad jääda töötlemata. Võtke arvesse, et iga tellimuse eest tuleb tasuda eraldi maksega.	Izdrukājiet šo lapu informācijai, jo, lai veiktu maksājumu, ir nepieciešami visi bankas rekvizīti. Pasūtījumi, kuros nebūs norādīta visa iepriekš minētā informācija, iespējams, netiks apstrādāti. Lūdzu, ņemiet vērā, ka par katru pasūtījumu ir jāmaksā atsevišķi.	To stran natisnite za vašo evidenco, saj so za izvedbo vašega plačila potrebni vsi bančni podatki. Naročila, oddana brez vseh zgornjih podatkov, morda ne bodo obdelana. Prosimo, upoštevajte, da lahko z enim plačilom plačate le eno naročilo.
static.eftPaymentInstructionRefThreat	Sørg for, at du bruge din <b>FIK</b> som reference, når du foretager betalingen. Hvis du ikke bruger denne betalingsreference, kan vi ikke behandle din betaling.	Please ensure you use your <b>Ref</b> as your reference when you make the payment. If you do not use this payment reference we will not be able to process you payment.				Vennligst bruk ditt <b>KID-nummer</b> som din referanse når du gjennomfører betalingen. Hvis du ikke bruker denne betalingsreferansen, vil vi ikke være i stand til å behandle betalingen.	Atlikdami mokėjimą elektroniniu būdu, įsitikinkite, kad kaip operacijos nuorodą naudojate savo nuorodos numerį. Jei šios nuorodos nenaudosite, negalėsime apdoroti mokėjimo.		Vermeld altijd uw betalingsreferentie als transactiereferentie wanneer u de betaling overmaakt. Als u dit referentienummer niet gebruikt, kunnen wij de betaling niet verwerken.			Bitte vergewissern Sie sich, dass Sie bei der Überweisung Ihre Zahlungsreferenz als Verwendungszweck eintragen. Wenn Sie diese Referenz nicht verwenden, können wir Ihre Zahlung nicht bearbeiten.	Varmista, että käytät <b>viitettäsi</b> maksaessasi maksua. Jos et käytä tätä maksun viitettä, emme pysty käsittelemään maksuasi.	Ti preghiamo di indicare la <b>causale</b> come riferimento quando effettui il pagamento. Se non usi la causale non saremo in grado di elaborare il pagamento.	Veuillez vous assurer que vous utilisez votre <b> référence</b> comme référence lorsque vous effectuez le paiement. Si vous n'utilisez pas cette référence de paiement, nous ne pourrons pas traiter votre paiement.	Asegúrese de utilizar la <b>número de referencia</b> como referencia cuando realice el pago. Si no utiliza este número de referencia, no podremos procesar su pago.	При осуществлении перевода денег электронным способом используйте ваш справочный номер в качестве номера операции. При несоблюдении этого требования мы не сможем обработать ваш платеж.	Använd ditt <b>OCR-nummer</b> som betalningsreferens vid din betalning. Om du inte använder denna referens kommer vi inte kunna slutföra din betalning.			Přesvědčte se, prosím, že jste u platebního příkazu vyplnili pro referenci svůj <b>variabilní symbol</b>. Pokud nepoužijete tento variabilní symbol, nebudeme schopni vaši platbu zpracovat.	Pri zadávaní platby sa uistite, že používate vaše <b>referenčné číslo platby</b> ako vašu referenciu. Ak toto referenčné číslo platby neuvediete, platbu nebude možné spracovať.	Kérjük, használja <b>fizetési referenciaszám</b> számát, amikor a pénzt átutalja. Amennyiben nem ezt a fizetési hivatkozási számot használja, kifizetését nem tudjuk feldolgozni.	Kasutage makse tegemisel oma <b>makseviide</b>. Kui te viitenumbrit ei kasuta, ei saa me teie makset töödelda.	Veicot maksājumu, lūdzu, pārliecinieties, vai kā atsauci izmantojat savu <b>Ats.</b> Ja neizmantosit šo maksājuma atsauci, mēs nevarēsim apstrādāt jūsu maksājumu.	Prosimo, prepričajte se, da pri izvedbi plačila uporabite <b>referenca za plačilo</b> kot svojo referenco. Če ne uporabite te reference za plačilo, morda ne bomo mogli obdelati vašega plačila.
static.eftResultHeader	Resultat	Result				Resultat	Rezultatas	Resultado	Resultaat			Ergebnis	Tulos	Risultato	Résultat	Resultado	Результат	Resultat			Výsledek	Výsledok	Eredmény	Tulemus	Rezultāts	Rezultat
static.eftResultInfo	Resultat af overførsel	Wire Transfer Result		Bpay Result	Resultado da Boleto Bancário	Resultat av bankoverføring	Pervedimo rezultatas	Resultado da transferência eletrônica	Resultaat bankoverschrijving	Fund Transfer Result		Überweisungsergebnis	Tilisiirto tulos	Risultato del bonifico bancario	Résultat du virement bancaire	Resultado de la transferencia bancaria	Результат электронного перевода	Resultat av betalning	Boleto Bancário Result		Výsledek telegrafického převodu	Elektronický prevod	Távirati utalás eredménye	Elektroonilise ülekande tulemus	Elektroniskā pārskaitījuma rezultāts	Rezultat elektronskega prenosa denarja
static.eftStartInstruction	Følg anvisninger på næste side, når du skal overføre penge til vores bankkonto.	Follow the instructions on the next page to transfer money to our bank account.		Follow the instructions on the next page to pay with Bpay.		Følg anvisningene på neste side for å overføre penger til vår bankkonto.	Vykdykite kitame puslapyje pateiktus nurodymus, kad pervestumėte pinigus į savo banko sąskaitą.	Siga as instruções na próxima página para transferir dinheiro para nossa conta corrente.	Volg de aanwijzingen op de volgende pagina om geld over te maken naar onze bankrekening.			Folgen Sie den Anleitungen auf der nächsten Seite, um Geld auf unser Bankkonto zu überweisen.	Noudata ohjeita seuraavalla sivulla siirtääksesi rahaa pankkitilillemme.	Segui le istruzioni alla pagina seguente per trasferire denaro sul nostro conto corrente.	Suivez les instructions de la page suivante pour transférer la somme sur notre compte bancaire.	Siga las instrucciones de la página siguiente para transferir el dinero a nuestra cuenta bancaria	Для перечисления денег на наш банковский счет следуйте инструкциям, приведенным на следующей странице.	Följ anvisningarna på nästa sida för att föra över pengar till vårt plusgirokonto.			Pro převod peněz na náš bankovní účet sledujte pokyny na další straně.	Na prevod peňazí na náš účet sa pridržiavajte inštrukcií pre platby na nasledujúcej strane.	A bankszámlánkra történő utaláshoz kövesse a következő oldalon található kifizetési utasításokat.	Raha ülekandmiseks meie pangakontole järgige järgmisel lehel esitatud juhiseid.	Izpildiet nākamajā lapā redzamos norādījumus, lai pārskaitītu naudu uz mūsu bankas kontu.	Za prenos denarja na naš bančni račun sledite navodilom na naslednji strani.
static.eftThankYou	Tak for din ordre hos os!	Thank you for ordering from us!				Takk for din bestilling hos oss!	Dėkojame, kad užsakėte pas mus!	Obrigado por comprar conosco!	Dank u voor uw bestelling bij ons.			Vielen Dank für Ihre Bestellung bei uns!	Kiitos, että tilasit meiltä!	Grazie per l'ordine!	Nous vous remercions d'avoir passé commande avec nous !	Gracias por realizar su pedido con nosotros	Благодарим вас за размещение заказа!	Tack för din beställning hos oss!			Děkujeme vám, že jste si objednali od nás!	Ďakujeme za vašu objednávku!	Köszönjük, hogy tőlünk rendelt!	Täname teid tellimuse eest!	Pateicamies, ka veicāt pasūtījumu pie mums!	Hvala, da ste pri nas oddali naročilo!
static.errorCode1	Forkerte betalingsoplysninger.	Incorrect payment details.	支付详情不正确。			Feil betalingsinformasjon.	Klaidinga mokėjimo informacija.	Detalhes de pagamento incorretos.	Onjuiste betaalgegevens.	결제 정보가 잘못되었습니다.		Einzelheiten zur ungültigen Zahlung.	Väärät maksutiedot.	Dati di pagamento non corretti.	Les données sont incorrectes.	Detalles de pago incorrecto.	Неверные данные для совершения платежа.	Felaktig batalnings info. Kontrollera att du angett rätt kortnummer, CVV-kod och utgångsdatum i MM sen ÅÅ.			Nesprávné upřesňující platební údaje.	Nesprávne údaje o platbe.	Hibás fizetési adatok.	Valed makseandmed.	Nepareiza detalizētā informācija par maksājumu.	Nepravilni podatki za plačilo.
static.errorCode2	Midlertidig fejl. Prøv igen senere.	Temporary error, try again in a short while.	临时错误，请稍后再试。			Midlertidig feil. Forsøk på nytt om en stund.	Laikina klaida. Palaukite ir bandykite dar kartą.	Erro temporário, tente novamente daqui a pouco.	Tijdelijke fout. Probeer het later nog eens.	일시적인 오류가 발생했습니다. 잠시 후 다시 시도하십시오.		Temporärer Fehler, versuchen Sie es bitte in Kürze noch einmal.	Väliaikainen virhe, yritä uudelleen vähän ajan kuluttua.	Errore temporaneo, riprovare tra poco.	Erreur système temporaire, s'il vous plaît essayer à nouveau plus tard.	"Error temporal; inténtelo de nuevo dentro de unos instantes."	Временная ошибка, повторите попытку через некоторое время.	Tillfälligt fel, var god försök senare.			Dočasná chyba, zopakujte pokus za chvilku.	Dočasná chyba, skúste opäť o chvíľu.	Ideiglenes hiba. Kérjük, próbálja meg később.	Ajutine tõrge. Proovige veidi aja pärast uuesti.	Pagaidu kļūda, pēc brīža mēģiniet vēlreiz.	Trenutna napaka. Prosimo, poskusite znova čez nekaj časa.
static.errorCode3	Din betaling blev afvist.	Your payment was declined.	您的付款被拒绝。			Din betaling ble avvist.	Mokėjimas atmestas.	Seu pagamento foi negado.	Uw betaling is afgewezen.	결제가 거부되었습니다.		Ihre Zahlung wurde abgelehnt.	Maksusi hylättiin.	Il pagamento non è stato accettato.	Votre paiement a été refusé.	Se ha denegado el pago.	Платеж отклонен.	Ogiltig betalning! Kontrollera eller ändra betalnings info.			Vaše platba byla odmítnuta.	Vaša platba bola zamietnutá.	Kifizetése elutasításra került.	Teie makse lükati tagasi.	Jūsu maksājums tika noraidīts.	Vaše plačilo je bilo zavrnjeno.
static.errorCodeUnknown	Der opstod en uventet fejl.	An unexpected error has occured.	发生未预料的错误。			Det har oppstått en uventet feil.	Įvyko netikėta klaida.	Um erro inesperado ocorreu.	Een onverwachte fout is opgetreden.	예기치 않은 오류가 발생했습니다.		Es ist ein unerwarteter Fehler aufgetreten.	Tapahtui odottamaton virhe.	Si è verificato un errore imprevisto.	Une erreur inattendue s'est produite.	Se ha producido un error inesperado.	Неожиданная ошибка.	Ett fel har uppstått. Om problemet kvarstår kontakta oss.			Došlo k neočekávané chybě.	Vyskytol sa nečakaný problém.	Váratlan hiba történt.	Ilmnes ootamatu tõrge.	Radusies neparedzēta kļūda.	Prišlo je do nepričakovane napake.
static.ewallet	e-wallet	e-wallet				e-lommebok	„e-wallet“					E-Wallet	e-lompakko	e-wallet	E-Wallet	monedero electrónico	Электронный кошелек	e-plånbok			elektronická peněženka 'e-wallet'	Elektronická peňaženka	e-pénztárca	e-rahakott	e-maks	e-denarnica
static.fik		FIK																								
static.iban		IBAN																								
static.ibpRedirectInfo	Du bliver stillet om, så du kan afslutte betalingen.	You will be redirected to finish your payment.	您将被重定向以完成付款。			Du vil bli ført videre for å avslutte betalingen.	Būsite nukreipti, kad užbaigtumėte mokėjimą.	Você será redirecionado para finalizar o pagamento.	U wordt omgeleid om de betaling te voltooien.	결제를 완료하기 위해 이동합니다.		Sie werden zur Durchführung der Zahlung umgeleitet.	Sinut ohjataan viemään maksusi loppuun.	Verrai reindirizzato a un altro sito per concludere il pagamento.	Vous sera transmis à votre banque pour compléter le processus de paiement.	Será redireccionado para finalizar el pago.	Для завершения платежа вы будете перенаправлены.	Du kommer skickas vidare till din bank för betalning.			Pro dokončení své platby budete přesměrováni.	Na dokončenie platby budete presmerovaný.	A kifizetés befejezéséhez az oldal átirányítódik.	Teid suunatakse makse lõpuleviimiseks edasi.	Jūs tiksit novirzīts, lai pabeigtu savu maksājumu.	Za dokončanje vašega plačila vas bomo preusmerili.
static.invalidAccountNr		Invalid account number																								
static.invalidBankBranchNr		Invalid branch number																								
static.issueNumber	Kortnummer	Issue number	发行号			Utstedelsesnummer	Išdavimo numeris	Número de emissão	Uitgavenummer	발행 번호		Ausgabenummer	Tapausnumero	Numero	Numéro d'émission	Número de envío	Номер выпуска	Utgivningsnummer			Číslo problému	Číslo výdaja	Kérdés száma	Väljaande number	Izsniegšanas numurs	Številka izdaje
static.javaScriptInfo	Din browser understøtter ikke JavaScript! Denne side kræver, at JavaScript er aktiveret i din browser!	Your browser does not support JavaScript! This page requires JavaScript to be enabled in your browser!	您的浏览器不支持JavaScript！该页面需要在您的浏览器中启用JavaScript！			Din nettleser støtter ikke JavaScript! Denne siden krever at JavaScript er aktivert i nettleseren!	Jūsų naršyklė nepalaiko „JavaScript“! Norint peržiūrėti šį puslapį, jūsų naršyklėje tur būti įgalintas „JavaScript“!	Seu navegador não é compatível com JavaScript! Para acessar esta página, você deve habilitar o JavaScript no seu navegador!	Uw browser ondersteunt geen JavaScript! Voor deze pagina moet u JavaScript in uw browser inschakelen.	브라우저가 JavaScript를 지원하지 않습니다. 브라우저에서 이 페이지를 보려면 JavaScript가 필요합니다.		JavaScript wird nicht von Ihrem Browser unterstützt. Für diese Seite muss JavaScript in Ihrem Browser aktiviert sein.	Selaimesi ei tue JavaScriptiä! Tämän sivun näkemiseksi selaimesi JavaScript on oltava päällä!	Il tuo browser non supporta JavaScript! Per essere abilitata dal browser questa pagina richiede JavaScript!	JavaScript n'est pas supporté par votre navigateur. être activé pour que cette page JavaScript dans votre navigateur.	Su navegador no acepta JavaScript. Esta página requiere que JavaScript esté habilitado en su navegador.	Ваш браузер не поддерживает JavaScript! Для отображения данной страницы необходимо включить JavaScript в браузере!	Din webläsare stöder inte JavaScript! Denna sida kräver att din webläsare stöder JavaScript!			Váš prohlížeč nepodporuje JavaScript! Tato strana vyžaduje, aby byl ve vašem prohlížeči JavaScript umožněn!	Váš prehliadač nepodporuje JavaScript! Zobrazenie tejto stránky vyžaduje vo vašom prehliadači podporu pre JavaScript!	Böngészője nem támogatja az JavaScript kódot. Az oldal a JavaScript használatát igényli, kérjük, hogy ezt engedélyezze a böngészőjében!	Teie brauser ei toeta JavaScripti! See leht nõuab, et teie brauseris oleks JavaScript lubatud.	Jūsu pārlūkprogramma neatbalsta JavaScript! Šai lapai nepieciešams, lai jūsu pārlūkprogrammā būtu iespējota valoda JavaScript!	Vaš spletni brskalnik ne podpira aplikacije JavaScript! Ta stran zahteva, da v vašem spletnem brskalniku omogočite aplikacijo JavaScript!
static.kidNummer		KID-nummer																								
static.kreditornummer		Kreditornummer																								
static.month	Måned	Month	月份			Måned	Mėnuo	Mês	Maand	월		Monat	Kuukausi	Mese	Mois	Mes	Месяц	Månad			Měsíc	Mesiac	Hónap	Kuu	Mēnesis	Mesec
static.numeroDeCompte		Numéro de Compte																								
static.numeroDeCuenta		Numero de cuenta																								
static.ocr		OCR																								
static.onlineBanking	Online bankaktiviteter	Online banking	网上银行			Nettbank	Internetinė bankininkystė	Banco on-line	Online bankieren	온라인 뱅킹		Online Banking	Verkkopankkipalvelut	Banca online	Services bancaires en ligne	Banca en línea	Банковские операции онлайн	Internetbank betalningar			Internetové bankovnictví	Online banking	Online bankolás	Interneti-pangandus	Tiešsaistes banku operācijas	Spletno bančništvo
static.orderAmount	Bestillingsbeløb	Order Amount				Ordrebeløp	Užsakymo suma	Valor do pedido	Som			Summe	Tilausmäärä	Importo ordine	Montant de la commande	Cantidad del pedido	Сумма заказа				Množství objednávek	Množstvo/suma na objednávke	A rendelés mennyisége	Tellimuse summa	Pasūtījuma summa	Količina naročila
static.orderDescription	Ordrebeskrivelse	Order description	订购说明			Ordrebeskrivelse	Užsakymo aprašas	Descrição do pedido	Omschrijving van de bestelling	주문 내용		Bestellung	Tilauksen kuvaus	Descrizione dell'ordine	Description Commander (Ordre)	Descripción del pedido	Описание заказа	Order beskrivning			Popis objednávky	Popis objednávky	Rendelés leírása	Tellimuse kirjeldus	Pasūtījuma apraksts	Opis naročila
static.orderId	Ordre-ID	Order ID	订购号			Bestillings-ID	Užsakymo ID	ID do pedido	Bestelling-ID	주문 ID		Bestellnummer	Tilaustunnus	ID ordine	ID de commande (ID d'ordre)	Identificador de pedido	№ заказа	Order id			Číslo objednávky	ID objednávky	Rendelés azonosítója	Tellimuse ID	Pasūtījuma ID	ID naročila
static.payPal	PayPal	PayPal				PayPal	„PayPal“						PayPal	PayPal	PayPal	PayPal					PayPal	PayPal	PayPal	PayPal	PayPal	PayPal
static.paymentInstruction	Betalingsanvisninger	Payment Instruction				Betalingsinstruksjon	Mokėjimo nurodymai	Instrução de pagamento					Maksuohjeet	Istruzioni per il pagamento	Instructions de paiement	Instrucciones de pago	Инструкции по оплате	Betalningsinstruktion			Platební pokyny	Inštrukcie pre platbu	Fizetési utasítások	Maksejuhis	Maksājuma instrukcija	Navodila za izvedbo plačila
static.paymentReceiver	Betalingsmodtager	Payment receiver				Betalingsmottaker	Įmokos gavėjas		Ontvanger van de betaling			Zahlungsempfänger	Maksun vastaanottaja	Destinatario del pagamento	Destinataire du paiement	Receptor del pago	Получатель платежа	Betalningsmottagare			Příjemce platby	Príjemca platby	Fizetés címzettje	Makse saaja	Maksājuma saņēmējs	Prejemnik plačila
static.paymentReceiverAccount	Kontonummer	Account number				Kontonummer	Sąskaitos numeris		Rekeningnummer			Kontonummer	Tilinumero	Numero conto	Numéro de compte	Número de cuenta	Номер счета				Číslo účtu	Číslo účtu	Számlaszám	Konto number	Konta numurs	Številka računa
static.paymentReceiverBank	Modtagende bank	Receiving bank				Mottakers bank	Gavėjo bankas		Ontvangende bank			Bank des Empfängers	Vastaanottava pankki	Banca ricevente	Banque réceptrice	Banco receptor	Банк получателя	Mottagande bank			Banka příjemce	Banka príjemcu	Fogadó bank	Saaja pank	Saņemošā banka	Banka za prejem
static.paymentRef	Betalingsreference	Payment reference		Ref		Betalingsreferanse	Nuorodos numeris		Betalingsreferentie			Verwendungszweck	Maksun viite	Causale del pagamento	Référence de paiement	Número de referencia	Справочный номер				Variabilní symbol	Referenčné číslo platby	Fizetési referenciaszám	Makseviide	Maksājuma atsauce	Referenca za plačilo
static.payout		Refund																								
static.payoutAccountStatementInfo		Your refund will be handled by Digital River World Payments AB. This name may appear on your account statement.																								
static.payoutConsentText		Payout consent text																								
static.plusgiro		Plusgiro																								
static.printButton	Udskriv denne side	Print this page				Skriv ut denne siden	Spausdinti	Imprimir	Afdrukken			Drucken	Tulosta tämä sivu	Stampa questa pagina	Imprimer cette page	Imprimir esta página	Печать	Skriv ut denna sida			Vytisknout tuto stránku	Vytlačiť túto stránku	Oldal nyomtatása	Prindi see leht	Izdrukājiet šo lapu	Natisni to stran
static.processingWait	Behandler! Vent venligst ...	Processing! Please wait...	正在处理！请稍候...			Behandling pågår! Vennligst vent...	Apdorojama! Palaukite...	Processando! Por favor, aguarde...	Bezig met de verwerking! Even geduld...	처리 중입니다. 잠시만 기다리십시오.		Processing! Bitte warten Sie...	Käynnissä! Odota.	Elaborazione in corso! Attendere...	Traitement! S'il vous plaît patienter ...	Procesando. Por favor, espere...	Обработка! Подождите...	Skickar! Var vänlig vänta...			Zpracovává se! Čekejte, prosím...	Spracúva sa! Čakajte, prosím...	Feldolgozás. Kérjük, várjon...	Töötlemine. Palun oodake...	Notiek apstrāde! Lūdzu, uzgaidiet...	Postopek poteka! Prosimo, počakajte ...
static.refreshAndBackInfo	Vigtigt. Brug IKKE browserens knapper 'Opdater' og 'Tilbage'!	Important. Do NOT use browser 'Refresh' and 'Back' buttons!	重要信息。切勿使用浏览器的“刷新”和“后退”按钮！			Viktig. Du må IKKE bruke nettleserens knapper 'Oppdater' og 'Tilbake'!	Svarbu. NENAUDOKITE naršyklės mygtukų 'Refresh' (Atnaujinti) ir 'Back' (Atgal)!	Importante. NÃO use os botões 'Atualizar' e 'Voltar' do navegador!	Belangrijk. Klik NIET op de knoppen 'Vernieuwen' en 'Terug' in uw browser!	중요. 브라우저의 '새로 고침' 및 '뒤로' 단추를 사용하지 마십시오.		Wichtig! Drücken Sie während des Zahlvorgangs NICHT auf 'Erneutes Laden' oder 'Zurück' in Ihrem Browser.	Tärkeää. Älä käytä selaimen 'Refresh' ja 'Back' -painikkeita!	Importante. NON usare i pulsanti del browser 'Aggiorna' e 'Indietro' !	"Important! Appuyez sur pendant le processus de paiement, et non sur  '' Recharger 'ou '  ""Précédent"" dans votre navigateur."	Importante: NO use los botones del navegador 'Recargar esta página' ni 'Ir a la página anterior'	Важно. НЕ нажимайте в браузере кнопки 'Обновить' и 'Назад' !	Viktigt. Använd INTE webläsarens 'Uppdatera sidan' eller 'Tillbaka' knapparna!			Důležité. NEPOUŽÍVEJTE v prohlížeči tlačítka 'Obnovit (Refresh)' a 'Zpět (Back)'!	"Dôležité. NEPOUŽÍVAJTE tlačidlá „obnoviť"" alebo „späť""!"	Fontos! NE használja böngészője 'Frissítés' vagy 'Vissza' gombját!	NB! ÄRGE kasutage brauseri nuppe Värskenda ja Tagasi!	Svarīgi! NEIZMANTOJIET pārlūkprogrammas pogu Atsvaidzināt un Atpakaļ!	Pomembno! V spletnem brskalniku NE UPORABLJAJTE gumbov 'Osveži' in 'Nazaj'!
static.returnToMerchant		Back to merchant					Grįžti į parduotuvę		Terug naar handelaar			Zurück zum Online Shop			Retour à la boutique		Назад к странице продавца	Återvänd till handlaren			Vrátit se k obchodníkovi	Návrat na stránku obchodníka	Vissza a kereskedőhöz	Tagasi kauplusse	Atgriezties pie pārdevēja	Vrni trgovcu
static.rib		RIB																								
static.sendCheckTo		Send your check to													Veuillez envoyer votre règlement à						Zašlete svůj šek na adresu	Pošlite šek	A csekket erre a címre küldje	Saatke tšekk aadressil	Nosūtiet savu čeku	Ček pošljite na naslov
static.submit	Send	Confirm	发送			Send	Siųsti	Confirmar	Versturen	보내기		Senden	Lähetä	Invia	Envoyer	Enviar	Отправить	Skicka			Potvrdit	Potvrdiť	Megerősítés	Kinnita	Apstiprināšana	Potrdi
static.thisLink		this link																			tento odkaz (link)	tento link	ez a hivatkozás	seda linki,	šī saite	to povezavo
static.title	Betaling	Payment	支付			Betaling	Mokėjimas		Betaling	결제		Zahlung	Maksu	Pagamento	Paiement	Pago	Оплата	Betalning			Platba	Platba	Fizetés	Makse	Maksājums	Plačilo
static.toOpenSlip		to open up your Boleto slip in a seperate window.			Clique neste link para abrir o Boleto em uma janela separada.																otevřít svůj Boleto skluz ve zvláštním okně	pre otvorenie Boleto sklzu v samostatnom okne.	a Boleto cédula megnyitása külön ablakban.	et avada maksekorraldus eraldi aknas.	lai atsevišķā logā atvērtu savu Boleto kvīti.	da se potrdilo o plačilu odpre v novem oknu.
static.year	År	Year	年份			År	Metai	Ano	Jaar	년		Jahr	Vuosi	Anno	Année	Año	Год	År			Rok	Rok	Év	Aasta	Gads	Leto
static.sepaMandate		SEPA Direct Debit Mandate							Mandaat Europese incasso			SEPA-Einzugsermächtigung														
static.creditor		Creditor							Crediteur			Gläubiger														
static.creditorIdHeading		Identifier of the Creditor							Id van de crediteur			Gläubiger-Identifikationsnr														
static.mandateReference		Mandate Reference							Mandaatreferentie			Mandatsreferenz														
static.billingInfo		Billing Info							Factuurinfo			Info zur Rechnung														
static.firstName		First Name							Voornaam			Vorname														
static.lastName		Last Name							Achternaam			Nachname														
static.email		Email							E-mail			E-mail														
static.address1		Address 1							Adres 1			Adresse 1														
static.address2		Address 2							Adres 2			Adresse 2														
static.zip		Zip							Postcode			PLZ														
static.countryCode		Country							Land			Land														
static.mandateConsentText		By signing this mandate form, you authorise (A) the Creditor to send instructions to your bank to debit your account and (B) your bank to debit your account in accordance with the instructions from the Creditor. As part of your rights, you are entitled to a refund from your bank under the terms and conditions of your agreement with your bank. A refund must be claimed within 8 weeks starting from the date on which your account was debited. Your rights are explained in a statement that you can obtain from your bank.							Door ondertekening van dit mandaatformulier geeft u toestemming aan (A) de crediteur om een opdracht te sturen naar uw bank om uw rekening te debiteren en (B) uw bank om een bedrag van uw rekening te debiteren in overeenstemming met de opdracht van de crediteur. U kunt een Europese incasso laten terugbetalen in overeenstemming met de algemene voorwaarden van uw overeenkomst met uw bank. Een verzoek tot terugbetaling moet binnen 8 weken na de debiteringsdatum worden ingediend. Uw rechten staan vermeld in een verklaring die u bij uw bank kunt aanvragen.			Mit der Unterzeichnung dieses Mandatformulars berechtigen Sie (A) den Gläubiger, Ihrer Bank Anforderungen zur Belastung Ihres Kontos zu senden und (B) Ihre Bank, Ihr Konto entsprechend den Anweisungen des Gläubigers zu belasten. Im Rahmen Ihrer Rechte haben Sie gemäß den Bestimmungen in der Vereinbarung mit Ihrer Bank Anspruch auf eine Erstattung. Eine Erstattung muss innerhalb von acht Wochen ab dem Datum der Belastung Ihres Kontos angefordert werden. Ihre Rechte sind in einer Erklärung, die Sie bei Ihrer Bank anfordern können, erläutert.														
static.ddAgreement		I have read and understood the terms and conditions of this SEPA Direct Debit Mandate and I agree to be bound by it. I approve my account to be debited for the amount of my purchase at minimum 6 business days from the date the order is placed. If my purchase is for a subscription product, I agree to have each recurring payment also debited from my account on the date of renewal.							Ik heb de algemene voorwaarden van dit mandaat Europese incasso gelezen en begrepen en ga ermee akkoord dat ik hieraan ben gebonden. Ik ga ermee akkoord dat het bedrag van mijn aankoop ten minste 6 werkdagen na plaatsing van de bestelling op mijn account in rekening wordt gebracht. In geval van de aanschaf van een productabonnement ga ik ermee akkoord dat elke periodieke betaling eveneens op de verlengingsdatum op mijn account in rekening wordt gebracht.			Ich habe die Geschäftsbedingungen dieser SEPA-Einzugsermächtigung gelesen, verstanden und anerkannt. Ich bestätige, dass mein Konto mit dem Betrag meines Kaufs mindestens sechs Geschäftstage nach der Platzierung der Bestellung belastet werden soll. Wenn mein Kauf für ein Abonnementprodukt gilt, bestätige ich, dass meine wiederkehrenden Zahlungen am Tag der Erneuerung ebenfalls meinem Konto belastet werden sollen.														
static.ddAgreementResult		You have read and understood the terms and conditions of this SEPA Direct Debit Mandate and agreed to be bound by it. You have approved your account to be debited for the amount of your purchase at minimum 6 business days from the date the order is placed. If your purchase is for a subscription product, you have agreed to have each recurring payment also debited from your account on the date of renewal.							U hebt de algemene voorwaarden van dit mandaat Europese incasso gelezen en begrepen en gaat ermee akkoord dat u hieraan bent gebonden. U gaat ermee akkoord dat het bedrag van uw aankoop ten minste 6 werkdagen na plaatsing van deze bestelling op uw account in rekening wordt gebracht. In geval van de aanschaf van een productabonnement gaat u ermee akkoord dat elke periodieke betaling eveneens op de verlengingsdatum op uw account in rekening wordt gebracht.			Sie haben die Geschäftsbedingungen zu dieser SEPA-Einzugsermächtigung gelesen, verstanden und als verbindlich akzeptiert. Sie haben bestätigt, dass Ihr Konto mit dem Betrag Ihres Kaufs mindestens sechs Geschäftstage nach der Platzierung der Bestellung belastet werden soll. Wenn Ihr Kauf für ein Abonnementprodukt gilt, haben Sie bestätigt, dass alle wiederkehrenden Zahlungen am Tag der Erneuerung ebenfalls Ihrem Konto belastet werden sollen.														
static.invalidBic		Invalid BIC							Ongeldig BIC			Ungültig BIC														
static.invalidIban		Invalid IBAN							Ongeldig IBAN			Ungültig IBAN														
static.invalidFirstName		Invalid first name							Ongeldige voornaam			Ungültiger Vorname														
static.invalidLastName		Invalid last name							Ongeldige achternaam			Ungültiger Nachname														
static.invalidAddress		Invalid address							Ongeldig adres			Ungültige Adresse														
static.invalidCity		Invalid city							Ongeldige plaats			Ungültiger Ort														
static.invalidZip		Invalid zip							Ongeldig postcode			Ungültig Postleitzahl														
static.invalidCountryCode		Invalid country							Ongeldig land			Ungültiges Land														
static.invalidEmail		Invalid email							Ongeldig e-mailadres			Ungültige E-Mail-Adresse														
static.invalidAgreement		You must agree to Terms and Conditions							U moet akkoord gaan met de algemene voorwaarden			Sie müssen den Geschäftsbedingungen zustimmen														
static.creditorId		[Creditor id]																								
static.creditorName		Digital River World Payments AB																								
static.creditorAddress		Textilgatan 31																								
static.creditorCity		Stockholm																								
static.creditorZipCode		120 30																								
static.creditorCountry		Sweden							Zweden			Schweden														
static.debtorName		Name of the debtor(s)							Naam van de debiteur(en)			Debitorname(n)														
static.debtorAddress		Street name and number							Straatnaam en huisnummer			Straße und Hausnummer														
static.debtorZipCity		Postal code and city/town							Postcode en plaats			Postleitzahl und Ort														
static.debtorDate		Date							Datum			Datum														
static.debtorBic		Swift BIC																								
static.debtorAccountNum		Account number IBAN							Rekeningnummer IBAN			Kontonummer IBAN														
static.ddResultInfo		Direct Debit Result							Resultaat automatische afschrijving			Ergebnis Lastschriftverfahren														
static.ddSupportedCountries		Aland Islands=FI,Austria=AT,Belgium=BE,Bulgaria=BG,Cyprus=CY,Czech Republic=CZ,Denmark=DK,Estonia=EE,Finland=FI,France=FR,French Guiana=FR,Germany=DE,Gibraltar=GI,Greece=GR,Guadeloupe=FR,Hungary=HU,Iceland=IS,Ireland=IE,Italy=IT,Latvia=LV,Liechtenstein=LI,Lithuania=LT,Luxembourg=LU,Malta=MT,Martinique=FR,Mayotte=FR,Monaco=MC,Netherlands=NL,Norway=NO,Poland=PL,Portugal=PT,Reunion=FR,Romania=RO,Saint Barthelemy=FR,Saint Martin (French part)=FR,Saint Pierre and Miquelon=FR,Slovakia=SK,Slovenia=SI,Spain=ES,Sweden=SE,Switzerland=CH,United Kingdom=GB							Aland=FI,Oostenrijk=AT,België=BE,Bulgarije=BG,Cyprus=CY,Tsjechië=CZ,Denemarken=DK,Estland=EE,Finland=FI,Frankrijk=FR,Frans Guyana=FR,Duitsland=DE,Gibraltar=GI,Griekenland=GR,Guadeloupe=FR,Hongarije=HU,Ijsland=IS,Ierland=IE,Italië=IT,Letland=LV,Liechtenstein=LI,Litouwen=LT,Luxemburg=LU,Malta=MT,Martinique=FR,Mayotte=FR,Monaco=MC,Nederland=NL,Noorwegen=NO,Polen=PL,Portugal=PT,Reunion=FR,Roemenië=RO,Saint-Barthélemy=FR,Sint Maarten (Franse deel)=FR,Saint Pierre en Miquelon=FR,Slowakije=SK,Slovenië=SI,Spanje=ES,Zweden=SE,Zwitserland=CH,Verenigd Koninkrijk=GB			Aland-Inseln=FI,Österreich=AT,Belgien=BE,Bulgarien=BG,Zypern=CY,Tschechische Republik=CZ,Dänemark=DK,Estland=EE,Finnland=FI,Frankreich=FR,Französisch-Guayana=FR,Deutschland=DE,Gibraltar=GI,Griechenland=GR,Guadeloupe=FR,Ungarn=HU,Island=IS,Irland=IE,Italien=IT,Lettland=LV,Liechtenstein=LI,Litauen=LT,Luxemburg=LU,Malta=MT,Martinique=FR,Mayotte=FR,Monaco=MC,Niederlande=NL,Norwegen=NO,Polen=PL,Portugal=PT,Réunion=FR,Rumänien=RO,St. Barthélemy=FR,St. Martin (französischer Teil)=FR,St. Pierre und Miquelon=FR,Slowakei=SK,Slowenien=SI,Spanien=ES,Schweden=SE,Schweiz=CH,Vereinigtes Königreich=GB														
static.termsAndCondition		Terms and Conditions							Bepalingen en voorwaarden			Geschäftsbedingungen														
static.onbehalfof		on behalf of [Merchant Name]							namens [Merchant Name]			im Auftrag von [Merchant Name]														
static.or		or																			nebo		vagy			
